Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Audio-Visual Materials 5922 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Audio-Visual Materials
1954-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board Fur and Leather Workers
5922 AV
0.83 cubic feet
0.8 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
8212304
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5685: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5917 P: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5685 P: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Photographs 6214 MB: Herbert Turkel Collection of a Fur Worker's Flesher's Knife, Memorabilia 5922: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional records 5922 MB: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Memorabilia
Fur workers -- Labor unions; Leather workers -- Labor unions; Harris, Walter; International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada; Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union.
8212304
- Retirement - Problems and Joy - May 1972, 1 (Box 1)
- Tom Myers, 2 (Box 1)
- Speak Out - Feb. 17, 1972, 3 (Box 1)
- Problems and Pleasures - Retirement - May 16, 1968, 4 (Box 1)
- How I spent the Summer - Sept. 1970, 5 (Box 1)
- Safeguard - Fun and Song - Oct. 1969, 6 (Box 1)
- Speak Out 1969, 7 (Box 1)
- XMHS - Hanukkah - 1968/69, 8 (Box 1)
- Sing along birthday - Jan. 1971, 9 (Box 1)
- How we spent summer - Nov. 1971, 10 (Box 1)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, May 24, 1954, 1 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, May 7, 1954, 2 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, April 9, 1954, 3 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, April 9, 1954, 4 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, May 20, 1954, 5 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, May 20, 1954, 6 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, May 23, 1954, 7 (Box 2)
- CIO - Harzinski, 8 (Box 2)
  Scope and Contents
  2 albums
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, June 11, 1954, 9 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO: May 7, 1954, 10 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, May 13, 1954, 11 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO - April 3, 1954, 12 (Box 2)
- April 2, 1954, 13 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO: April 28, 1954, 14 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO - May 13, 1954, 15 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO - May 7, 1954, 16 (Box 2)
- CIO Speech - 24 March 1954, 17 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - April 16, 1954, 18 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO: May 13, 1954, 19 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - April 9, 1954, 20 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO - April 23, 1954, 21 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - April 9, 1954, 22 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, May 13, 1954, 23 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - April 16, 1954, 24 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, April 28, 1954, 25 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, April 28, 1954, 26 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, April 23, 1954, 27 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, April 23, 1954, 28 (Box 2)
- Walter Harris - CIO: April 28, 1954, 29 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, April 16, 1954, 30 (Box 2)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, June 11, 1954, 31 (Box 2)
- April 2, 1954, 32 (Box 2)
- CIO Speech - 24 March 1954, 33 (Box 2)
- F & LW Speech: 24 March 1954, 34 (Box 2)
- Woolis - April 2, 1954, 35 (Box 2)